https://rent1sale1.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
We value the trust you place in Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™. That’s why we insist upon the highest standards for secure transactions and customer information privacy. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices. Note: Our privacy policy is subject to change at any time. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically.1. Collection of Personally Identifiable InformationWe collect personally identifiable information (email address) from you when you set up a free account with Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™. While you can browse some sections of our site without being a registered member, certain activities (such as searching for properties, viewing property contact information, and registering a property) do require registration.Rent1Sale1.com Renters:Our site requires you to give us contact information (email address). We use this information to create a unique user account, and to send you relevant property listings, reward claim reminders, and offers for moving-related services.Rent1Sale1.com Owners & Managers:Our site’s registration form requires you to give us contact information (name, address, phone number, and email address.) We use this information to notify you about communication from Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™ buyers and renters, and enable Rent1Sale1.com buyers and renters to view your property’s listing.We use your billing and financial information to invoice you for products and services that you purchase through the site.2. Use of Demographic and Profile DataWe use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you. We use your personal information to troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; customize your experience; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; and enforce our terms and conditions.In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users’ activity on our website.We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like zip code, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in – and to display content according to your preferences.CookiesA “cookie” is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™ places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer’s hard drive. Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty’s™ cookies do not contain any of your personally identifiable information.Our permanent cookies allow us to provide personalized features, such as automatically logging you into your personalized Start page. In order to use this feature, you must set your browser’s preferences to allow permanent cookies. You will still be able to use the site if you block permanent cookies.We also use temporary cookies (a.k.a. “per-session cookies”) to improve the functionality and usability of our site. These temporary cookies are permanently erased from your computer as soon as you log out of your Rent 1 & Sale 1 Realty™ account or link to a different website from your parent browser window. In order to use Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™, you must set your browser’s preferences to allow per-session cookies (most Web browsers automatically accept cookies).We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads on our behalf. These companies may employ cookies and action tags (also known as single pixel gifs or web beacons) to measure advertising effectiveness. Any information that these third parties collect via cookies and action tags is completely anonymous. If you would like more information about this practice and your choices, click here.3. Sharing of personal informationWe may share personal information withour other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal process. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™ and its affiliates will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur, that other business entity (or the new combined entity) will be required to follow this privacy policy with respect to your personal information.4. Links to Other SitesOur site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™ is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.5. Questions?Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address:Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty™8401 Lake Worth RoadSuite 228Lake Worth, FL 33467
For all your Residential Real Estate needs...
Site Map
Privacy Policy
Rent 1 Sale 1 Realty - Copyrights © 2020 . All rights reserved.
Facebook-f
